Sumegha Sakhreliya Gondaliya

Address ECC Road, Whitefield, Bangalore, KA - 560066

Phone +91 910 628 0625

E-mail sumegha137@gmail.com

Website https://sumegha13.github.io/SumeghaSakhreliyaGondaliya

Versatile developer with over 5 years of leveraging software engineering and implementing new technologies to maximize development efficiency. Acquiring and applying new complex technology concepts in a short period of time. Well-educated in website issue troubleshooting, root cause analysis and corrective action implementation. Seeking to apply expertise and extensive experience in software engineering to take on a challenging new role with a growing team.

Skills

.NET Framework Asp .NET, C# , MVC, NET Core, LINQ, .NET Console Application, WEB API

Reporting Tools SSRS, RDLC

UI/Front End HTML, CSS, JQuery, AJAX, JavaScript, BootStrap, Plugins

Back End Tool & Connectivity EF with/without Model, SQL Server Management Studio, My SQL **Service Integration in Project** Singal R Chat, Mail Merging, SMS, Email Service, SharePoint

Project Management Tools ZOHO, JIRA Version Control Tools Bitbucket, Git

Basic Knowledge Micro services, XAMARIN, Angular

Work History

Team Lead January 2020 to Current

Concentrix India Pvt. Ltd Bengaluru, KA

- Orchestrated efficient large-scale software deployments, including testing features and correcting code.
- Planned and developed interfaces that simplified overall management and offered ease of use.
- Monitored ongoing operation of assigned programs and responded to problems by diagnosing and correcting logic and coding errors.
- Evaluated project requirements and specifications and developed software applications that surpassed client expectations.
- Collaborate with different teams to meet the timelines with quality.

Software Analyst

Coolsoft Technologies Pvt. Ltd Bengaluru, KA

December 2018 to January 2020

- Created customized development frameworks for customers based on specific business goals and budgetary
 constraints
- Designed, developed and integrated software solutions based on business requirements and objectives.
- Completed software development lifecycle from requirement analysis to test planning, test case development and test execution
- Developed and implemented workflow templates, prioritizing efficiency and ease-of-use for end-users.
- Worked closely with business users and business analysts to understand functionality and propose creative solutions to meet business needs.

Assistant Professor

July 2014 to June 2015

Uka Tarsadia University Baradoli, GJ

- Used a variety of learning modalities and support materials to facilitate learning process and accentuate presentations, including visual, aural and social learning strategies.
- Performed research to serve as basis for academic writing for publication.
- Helped struggling students by providing support outside of classrooms and consistently checking in on progress.
- Applied innovative teaching methods to encourage student learning objectives. ss

RaInfotech Pvt. Ltd Surat, GJ

- Collaborated with project managers to select ambitious, but realistic coding milestones on pre-release software project development.
- Participated in cross-functional projects while working in lean development environments.
- Planned and developed interfaces that simplified overall management and offered ease of use.
- Translated verbal customer requirements into written use cases and testable development stories.

Projects Handled

Concentrix Onboarding Tool

Technology: Web Based Application (ASP.NET 4.0/C#, JavaScript, HTML, JQuery, Web Service Architecture, MVC, SQL Server, LINQ, Mail Merging and SharePoint Access)

Workforce Management tool (WFM)

Technology: Web Based Application (ASP.NET 4.0/C#, JavaScript, HTML, JQuery, Web Service Architecture, MVC, SQL Server and LINQ)

• Global Nomination tool (GNT)

Technology: Web Based Application (ASP.NET Core 3.1, LINQ, Angular and SQL Server)

CoolWorks

Technology: Web Based Application (ASP.NET 4.0/C#, JavaScript,AJAX, CSS, JQuery,JavaScript, HTML, SQL Server 2017)

PrimerolN (WEB + Mobile Application)

Technology: Web Based Application (ASP.NET MVC 5.2.1, Entity Framework 6.0, LINQ, JQuery, Ajax, C#, SQL Server 2017) + Mobile Application (XAMARIN)

JOBCHIME

Technology: Web Based Application (ASP.NET MVC 3.0,Telerik Components, CSS, C# , JavaScript, HTML, SQL Server 2010)

Education

Parul University - Gujarat TechnologicalUniversity

August 2012 to June 2014

Master of Engineering Information Technology

CPI: 8.5 - College Topper

Relevant Coursework Completed: Vehicular Ad-hoc Network (VANET)

Shri S'ad Vidya Mandal Institute of Technology - South Gujarat University

June 2007 to July 2011

Bachelor of Engineering Information Technology
Aggregate Percentage: 71.22 % - College Topper

Relevant Coursework Completed: ASP.NET C#

Awards & Accomplishments

- Awarded as Concentrix Unsung Hero for hard work, great team player and helping new joinees in team to learn thing fast by concentrix in June - 2021
- Awarded by **Concentrix** for being a quick learner and becoming a core part of the team in a short time, 100 % commitment towards the project in July 2020.
- Research Paper titled "PKI-SC: Public Key Infrastructure with Symmetric Key Cryptography Algorithm" has been presented in IEEE- ICCIC 2014 conference at Coimbatore and got Best Paper award.
- 2 National Conferences and 3 International Paper Publications.
- Basketball team player at District Level .